<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reijun</title>
    <link>https://reijun.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on reijun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 13:22:30 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://reijun.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>In Retrospect</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/post/in-retrospect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 13:22:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/post/in-retrospect/</guid>
      <description>It started off with a selection interview, then an orientation lunch, followed by 3 full days of monthly classes over the course of 7 months, from March to September. It ended (for now) with writing and presenting a plan. 3 more months of mentoring and learning group session to go.
Here are my thoughts on this interesting and fortuitous learning journey that has defined much of my 2021.
 Selection Interview</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspired</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/post/inspired/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 13:22:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/post/inspired/</guid>
      <description>I was recommended this book by a supervisor I had. I think of it as a farewell present from the supervisor I worked with for close to 2 years. The first 2 years of work that was not the most smooth sailing, but I have seen my growth that has not come very easily.
The book is kind of like a manual on how to be a product manager, with job descriptions of each member of a product team; tools, methods and processes used by the team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Reference</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/post/reference-website-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 13:22:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/post/reference-website-commands/</guid>
      <description>This page summarises the commands used to build this site to save time on looking up as this writer posts too infrequently and forgets.
 Website creating commands To create new post:
hugo new post/my-first-post.md
and edit new markdown file after.
To start hugo server with drafts enabled:
hugo server -D
and navigate to http://localhost:1313/.
To build static pages:
hugo -D
then copy to repository and push.
 Markdown and Style Guide Use H4 for headings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bye to 2020</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/post/new-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 18:23:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/post/new-2021/</guid>
      <description> Got a full time permanent position CNY dinner with family and coworkers, last with grandpa Colleague joined and quit within 2 months Empty trains and food places before lockdown Lockdown for 2 months Went to work half day, 1 day, 2 days, 3 days a week Many colleagues quit Applied twice and failed Got a job offer but got scammed to not take it Did new stuff Wear black masks Lose and gained weight Hattenna for christmas Less meetings Found pinkbear  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books I have read</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/post/reading-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 10:37:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/post/reading-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I have a folder of notes which I use to record my thoughts on some book I read. Here are a collection of those notes for books I read in 2018 and 2019. Much spoilers, please skip if you intend to read. I don&amp;rsquo;t agree with everything I wrote back then, but here they are~
Who moved my cheese Simple simple story of not overthink, feel sorry for yourself, and let emotions cloud your judgment, decisions and actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden path</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/post/golden-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 18:37:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/post/golden-path/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write this post after watching Techlead explained The Golden Path. Everyone has a golden path which they know to follow towards their success. It could be following your parents’ instructions - study hard, get into a good school and get a respectable job. It could be following the footsteps of those we admire. It could be the goal we are woking towards.
Somehow, people get distracted and decide against that path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay hungry, stay foolish</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 18:37:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>When starting a new phase in life, the excitement and passion is high as everything is fresh and full of possibilities. It is an unavoidable fact of life that we would face many difficulties, spend a lot of effort and become exhausted. If it is possible, I would take a screenshot in life to remember the moment where I was not so tired, not so jaded, and without the entitlement of feeling I deserve recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://reijun.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 17:55:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reijun.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome I sometimes add posts to this webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>